[narrator] Heavens Arena.
The 251-story building,
which stands 991 meters tall
is a mecca for fighters.
When combatants win a fight,
they may advance by one class
and receive a corresponding reward.
After reaching the 100th floor,
they are assigned a private room.
And those contestants
who are skilled and fortunate enough
to reach the 200th floor,
earn the right to challenge
the strongest fighters, the Floor Masters,
in an intense battle for survival.
This is without a doubt
the best stage a warrior could ask for.
[theme song playing]
[Wing] Only one thing
can protect you from a user of Nen.
You must learn to use it yourself...
and use Ten for defense.
Otherwise...
Your body will be shattered
beyond all recognition.
AWAKENING x AND x POTENTIAL
[narrator] As the hour grows late,
Wing’s lecture has reached its climax.
They have until midnight.
Gon and Killua must learn
how to use Nen
before the clock strikes twelve.
Nen is a power that dwells
within every single human person.
However, at the present time,
only a few are capable
of using that power.
And because of their ability,
they are treated as geniuses,
leaders, psychics, sages,
and even super humans.
A power that dwells within everyone?
[Wing] Yes.
And there are means
by which to awaken this power.
But only two.
Either slowly and carefully or by force.
Zushi opted for the slow and careful path.
Not only was he a quick learner,
but he was tireless in his training,
so he was able to master Ten
in a very short time.
About six months.
But that’s way too long!
We need to learn Ten and pass Hisoka
and we’ve gotta do it before midnight!
Then it seems force is our only choice.
But is that gonna be fast enough?
Exactly how long it takes
is up to you and how well you learn
to contain your aura in that short time.
So, let’s get right to it, shall we?
I will begin your training
by transmitting my aura in your direction.
This is Hatsu, which you saw earlier.
And of course, it goes without saying that
because I wish you no harm,
I’ll go easy on you.
But this method is still a drastic one.
In other words,
I will attempt to shock you
into awakening.
I will rouse your sleeping bodies
with a jolt,
making it so
that you can perform Ten easily.
The reason I say ‘sleeping’
is that your aura nodes
are currently closed,
preventing the free flow of aura.
And so, you see
by transmitting my aura through you,
I am hoping to jolt those nodes
into an open position.
AURA NODES: NODES WITHIN BODY
WHICH RELEASE AURA.
Under normal circumstances you would
spend your time training, in meditation,
learning how to sense your own aura
that surrounds you,
slowly and carefully allowing
those nodes to fully open.
Even a natural talent like Zushi here,
required three months.
But considering your abilities,
you could’ve accomplished it
in a week or less.
Which is why it’s unfortunate
that we are being forced to use
the drastic method.
I don't really get it.
What’s the problem?
I thought faster is always better,
isn’t it?
This method is a cheat
and is highly frowned upon.
We are skipping the proper steps.
If I was inexperienced
or bore any malicious intent,
I could kill you.
Yeah, but you aren’t inexperienced
or malicious.
So, we’re safe with you.
Right?
[sighs]
And that’s why I’ve been wondering…
ENVELOPE SUPPRESS
REFINE ACT
[Killua] What made you decide
to teach us the real Four Exercises
all of a sudden?
Because you are very close to getting it.
If you were to enter the 200th floor
without any of this knowledge,
you would suffer greatly.
You see, up there,
everyone knows how to manipulate Nen.
And it is customary
to initiate any new arrivals
who are ignorant of Nen
by attacking with it.
In other words,
they do what I am about to
but without the necessary restraint.
They do not care if people die.
It’s all the same to them.
Only those who prove
they are strong enough to survive
are welcome to stay there...
as the chosen.
They have paid a high price
for the privilege.
That is why it’s important for you
to be prepared.
I don’t expect any of that
was very encouraging
but through this method
I believe you will awaken.
It is clear you have the talent
and ability.
Take off your jackets, face away from me
and put down all your belongings.
[Gon] It’s so hot!
And I can feel this pressure,
even though I know Mister Wing
isn’t touching me.
[Killua] This is it!
That sensation…
It’s like some slimy, invisible thing
crawling across my skin.
Multiply this by a few million
and it’d feel exactly
like my brother’s Nen.
Now I’ll begin.
[strangled cry]
And now every Aura Node in your body
has been opened.
Thi-- This is…
That, gentlemen, is your aura,
also known as life energy.
You can see it now
because the nodes in your eyes
were also opened.
It almost looks like...
steam rising off the spout of a teakettle.
It’s so crazy!
It’s rushing out
from every part of my body!
And it doesn’t look like it’s stopping!
No way… This can’t be good!
What you see is your life energy,
so if it continues to escape,
you will become quite tired.
Expend all of your aura and you will
collapse from extreme fatigue.
Oh, I get it.
Listen to me carefully!
You must keep your focus
on containing your aura within your body.
Now close your eyes!
Use any stance you prefer.
Whatever helps you to maintain your focus.
Visualize your aura flowing through you
as if it were blood
flowing through your body.
From the top of your head
to your right shoulder,
to your hand,
through your legs
then up your left side.
And now visualize that flow
as little by little
it begins to gradually slow down
and swirl around your body.
These boys are incredible.
They didn’t even need me to tell them
that a natural stance
would be the most effective.
They’ve mastered the technique
after only a few simple directions.
It’s magnificent
and terrifying.
Now slowly open your eyes.
Tell me how you feel.
I feel like…
like I’m surrounded
by some viscous liquid.
It feels like
I’m wearing weightless clothes.
I want you both to continue
holding on to those images.
Once you assimilate them,
you’ll be able to do this in your sleep.
Next, I will proceed
to emit malicious Nen against you!
Before your nodes were forced open,
standing within this would’ve caused
excruciating pain.
Yeah, okay.
I get it now.
Your whole ‘blizzard’ analogy.
It makes sense.
[Wing] If you can fend off my Nen,
you will finally be able
to break through his barrier as well!
Prepare yourselves!
[Gon and Killua screaming]
[footsteps]
Mmm.
Welcome to the 200th floor.
Seems I needn’t bother
with the traditional initiation.
I think I can guess
why you’ve come to Heavens Arena.
You intended to get some training in
before challenging me, correct?
That’s right.
But I didn’t expect
I was gonna find you here.
That saves me some trouble.
[chuckles]
I wouldn’t get too brash
just because you learned to use Ten.
There is much to learn about Nen.
To be honest,
I feel absolutely no urge
to fight you right now.
However...
If you manage to win
a single match on this floor,
I’ll accept your challenge.
Let's go.
Newcomers?
Looks like it, huh?
[Riehlvelt] It appears they can use it.
[Sadso] Indeed…
RECEPTION DESK
Welcome to the 200th floor!
Please go ahead
and fill out all these forms.
So, would you like to register
for a match right now?
And because this level incorporates
a self-service system,
you’re permitted 90 whole days
of fight preparation.
During those ninety days
you can call me for a fight
any time you desire.
You’re free to fight every day, of course.
Or if you’d prefer,
you can wait until the very last minute.
It’s up to you!
Once you’ve participated in a fight,
your 90 days of preparation time
starts over again.
However, if you don’t fight
before the end of the 90 days,
you’ll be disqualified
and your name will be stricken
from all of the official records.
Wait, lemme get this straight.
We’re gonna have more than one fight
up on this level?
Yes.
The only way for you to clear this floor
is to rack up ten victories!
However, if you lose four times
before you secure ten wins,
you'll be disqualified.
[buzzer]
Also,
if you do win ten times,
your reward is that you’ll have a chance
to challenge the Floor Masters!
The Floor Masters
are the 21 strongest fighters
that Heavens Arena has to offer.
Each one
gets one whole floor to themselves
from 230 all the way to 250.
Are you starting to understand now?
If you’re able to beat a Floor Master,
you win the honor and privilege
of becoming the new master of that floor!
Uh... but wait, there’s more!
The Floor Masters enjoy other perks!
Not the least of which
is you’ll be eligible to participate
in the Battle Olympia,
the Biennial Festival of Combat!
Isn’t that so exciting?!
Huh? No reaction?!
Sure, whatever you say, lady.
Is there anything special
about the top floor?
That's what you want to know?
The champion of the Battle Olympia
gets to live on the top floor!
How about that?
It's an incredible honor!
A penthouse that’s a thousand meters up!
It’s a life of luxury!
Don't you get it?
Yeah, but Killua,
your house is like 3700 meters up,
isn’t it?
But-- But wait!
There are other prizes!
-The champion always receives--
-Well? Whaddya think?
I dunno.
If that’s the floor’s big secret,
-I don't care anymore.
-Ooh!
Yeah! I just want to fight with Hisoka!
Forget all that other stuff!
I don’t get it!
Why did the two of you
even bother to come here?
Well, I guess that means
you’re just gonna have to win a fight.
But you’re gonna wait
a little while first, aren’t you?
[Gon] No way…
I’m ready!
These opponents are different
and I’m not leaving
‘til I find out just how different!
In that case, I’ll need you
to fill out this form as well.
‘kay!
[clatter]
[Killua] You want something?
Oh, no. Not really.
We’re simply waiting in line,
so we can register for a match. Right?
[cackling]
[chuckling]
Oh, I get it now.
Hey, Gon.
I think these guys wanna fight
on the same day you do.
[cackling]
I'm ready.
Just let me know when I fight.
Well, you heard him.
That boy is brimming with energy, huh?
[slow cackling]
[chuckling]
Now, Mister Gon will be in room 2207
and Mister Killua in 2223.
We’ll let you know
which day your match is set.
Thanks a lot, Miss!
[Killua]
I’m willing to bet that those guys
must have gone
through the same tough initiation
Four-Eyes was talking about.
[keys jangling]
If we’d gone in blind,
we both could’ve ended up
exactly like they did.
Wow! This room is huge!
[Killua] Hey! Aren’t you listening?
Look at how sparkly the bathroom is!
Oh, wow!
I’ve never seen such a big bed
in my whole life!
Look, Killua!
[jingling signal]
Hey, Gon!
YOUR BATTLE HAS BEEN SET
FOR 3 P.M., MARCH 11!
What? Tomorrow?
That's fast.
[whoosh]
I don’t think I can win yet.
But that’s okay!
I just need the experience.
I need to find out
what I can do now that I have this power.
[cheering]
We’ve got a thrilling match
for you today, everyone!
First up is Gon,
who managed to zip straight to this floor
in no time at all!
His opponent will be Gido,
who currently holds a respectable record
of four wins and one loss!
[Gon stretching and grunting]
[cackling]
[Wing] Gon. Killua.
Listen to me.
Ten is only defensive.
In terms of offense
it will offer you no advantage.
It is also important to remember
physical attacks will still cause damage.
An opponent who is highly skilled
in the use of Nen,
will be able to penetrate your Ten
and can easily deal you a lethal blow.
That’s why you should wait two months
before you start fighting.
During that time
I will teach you as much as I’m able.
[Gon] I’m really sorry, Mister Wing.
But I’m itching for a fight right now!
Goodness gracious.
That boy’s a real handful.
And... begin!
[cheering]
[roaring]
[cackling]
DANCING SPINNING TOPS
[commentator]
There they are, Gido's Dancing Tops!
He uses an arsenal
of dangerous spinning tops
to attack his opponent
and crush them into submission!
Here we go.
Battle Waltz!
[gasps]
[grunts in pain]
[rasping in pain]
Clean hit!
[commentator] Gon gives up a hit!
One point to Gido!
He’s sure not wasting any time!
Gon’s off to a rough start!
[groans quietly]
[Gido] I can use Nen
to keep these tops
attacking you for hours.
The attack pattern
is so incredibly complex
that no one knows
what they’ll do next!
Not even me!
The tops are bouncing off each other
and attacking me.
They might be small,
but they pack a big punch.
Like a hammer!
[narrator] Gon has begun his first battle
on the 200th floor,
which is filled with Nen users.
It’s nothing at all like he expected.
Will Gon survive this predicament?
Or suffer defeat?
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we’ll be introducing Gido!
He fights with tops controlled by Nen!
Maybe he’ll turn himself
into one and spin into you!
[both] Spin round and round!
[Gon] Next time:
"Fierce x And x Ferocious."
[Killua] Just don’t be too reckless.
[Gon] A real friend would want me
to be reckless.
[Killua] Okay, that’s reckless.